<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corona Help App</string>
    <string name="description">profile image</string>
    <string name="status">Status:</string>
    <string name="menuDescription">menu image</string>
    <string name="self_test">Self Check</string>
    <string name="report_a_case">Report a case</string>
    <string name="virus_symptoms">Virus Symptoms</string>
    <string name="precautions">Precautions</string>
    <string name="news_update">News Update</string>
    <string name="movement_history">Movement History</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>

    <string name="text_sample">
        Excepteur sint officia fugiat laboris voluptate pariatur. Ex voluptate cupidatat
        est laborum et non commodo. Officia fugiat nisi consequat occaecat eu.
</string>
    <string name="start_test">Start Check</string>
    <string name="title_activity_location_history">Map</string>
    <string name="location_history">Location History</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_coro">Welcome to Coro</string>
    <string name="care">Care</string>
    <string name="enter_your_fullname">Enter Your Fullname</string>
    <string name="enter_your_phone_number">Enter Your Phone Number</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender:</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="text_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="not_home">No maybe later</string>
    <string name="are_you_at_home">Are you at home?</string>
    <string name="upload_a_profile_picture">Upload a profile picture</string>
    <string name="coro">Coro</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>


    <string name="precaution_1">
        "Regularly and thoroughly clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand rub or wash them with soap and water.
        Why? Washing your hands with soap and water or using alcohol-based hand rub kills viruses that may be on your hands.
    </string>

    <string name="precaution_2">
        "Maintain at least 1 meter (3 feet) distance between yourself and anyone who is coughing or sneezing.
        Why? When someone coughs or sneezes they spray small liquid droplets from their nose or mouth which may contain the virus. If you are too close, you can breathe in the droplets, including the COVID-19 virus if the person coughing has the disease.
    </string>

    <string name="precaution_3">
         "Avoid touching eyes, nose and mouth.
        Why? Hands touch many surfaces and can pick up viruses. Once contaminated, hands can transfer the virus to your eyes, nose or mouth. From there, the virus can enter your body and can make you sick.

    </string>

    <string name="precaution_4">
        "Make sure you, and the people around you, follow good respiratory hygiene. This means covering your mouth and nose with your bent elbow or tissue when you cough or sneeze. Then dispose of the used tissue immediately.
        Why? Droplets spread the virus. By following good respiratory hygiene you protect the people around you from viruses such as cold, flu and COVID-19.

    </string>

    <string name="precaution_5">
         "Stay home if you feel unwell. If you have a fever, cough and difficulty breathing, seek medical attention and call in advance. Follow the directions of your local health authority.
        Why? National and local authorities will have the most up to date information on the situation in your area. Calling in advance will allow your health care provider to quickly direct you to the right health facility. This will also protect you and help prevent the spread of viruses and other infections.

    </string>

    <string name="precaution_6">
        "Keep up to date on the latest COVID-19 hotspots (cities or local areas where COVID-19 is spreading widely). If possible, avoid traveling to places  – especially if you are an older person or have diabetes, heart or lung disease.
        Why? You have a higher chance of catching COVID-19 in one of these areas.

    </string>
    <string name="report_string">Please select your state and a number below to reach NCDC office nearest to you</string>

    <string name="state_prompt">Select your state</string>
    <string name="state_prompt2">Select a number to call</string>
    <string name="test_count">Check: 1/x</string>
    <string name="rd_text_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="rd_text_no">No</string>


</resources>
